A Guide to the Oscar M. Ruebhausen Papers FA077
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Dartmouth College
  - 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - 1993-1998 (Box 20, Folder 164)
- Untitled (closed box) (Box 21)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted material.
- Untitled (closed box) (Box 22)